<referees>
    <linkedin>
        <item>
            <person>
                Mohamed Louati
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-louati-consultant
            </profile>
            <title>
                Senior Web development consultant,
                worked with Gregory for the client BNPP
            </title>
            <text>
                "I've had the pleasure to get acquainted with Gregory during an assignment
                for BNPP group. I liked his thorougnness and the efficiency he's got to 
                design and develop. 
                As a Lead developer and technical referee of the team, he has been essential
                to build this solution which was particularly complex and restrictive (security limitations,
                add strong ciphering capabilities in a web environment).
                He was also confortable with Agile methodologies, and luckily he has been
                able to take over and play the role of scrum master when came a need
                to compensate the shortcomings of the customer in this matter."
                --16 Mai 2017
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Kamel Gharbi
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/kamel-gharbi-14714554/
            </profile>
            <title>
                Architect Developer,
                worked with Gregory for the client BNPP
            </title>
            <text>
                "I joined Gregory as a team member in a sensitive BNPP project.
                What struck me immediately was his perfect mastery of the subject as well as his strong 
                commitment in its success ahead. Gregory has all the necessary required knowledge in IT, 
                concerning front as well as back end oriented technologies, and he can reply to the most 
                complex needs of his customer. It has been his assignments to integrate new components and 
                procedures in our framework and he did that, remarkably adapting to this aspect.
                Gregory has also a great deal of sense of humor yet maintains himself always professionel. 
                He has the capacity to lead and plan discussions to guide everyone in the team, and at the 
                same time he can step aside from time to time. I'll always be happy to work with Gregory."
                --March 16, 2017
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Patterson Waltz
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/jpwaltz/
            </profile>
            <title>
                Senior Process Improvement Consultant / Coach,
                worked with Gregory for the client BNPP
            </title>
            <text>
                "During the many months I provided Scrum coaching to a development project team 
                of which Gregory was a key member, I witnessed his attention to detail as well as 
                his constant striving for technical excellence. I was also repeatedly impressed with is efforts 
                to seek out ways to reduce or remove impediments to his teams' productivity."
                --January 12, 2017
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Matthieu Charlier
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthieu-charlier-69624265
            </profile>
            <title>
                Senior Consultant - Capital Markets,
                worked with Gregory for the client BNPP
            </title>
            <text>
                "I had the opportunity to work with Gregory on a sensitive project for the General Inspection 
                of a major european bank. 
                Gregory always showed high motivation on the project and proved to be very Agile 
                during the development phase. What I really appreciated is that he did not only 
                took into consideration the business requirements, but also aimed at building a technically 
                sustainable and flexible solution for the future."
                --October 25, 2016
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Samuel Herve
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/samuelherve
            </profile>
            <title>
                Java/JEE/AEM Technical Lead,
                worked with Gregory at Aptea
            </title>
            <text>
                "I had the pleasure to work together with Gregory where he was project manager. 
                He has been able to handle a very complex business analysis, successfuly driving the client 
                requirements progress with the project pace. 
                Gregory is thoroughly involved on the project he's working on, and a infallible team motivator. 
                He's also been a very pleasant day-to-day workmate, I wish him the best in his career."
                --September 7, 2016
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Loic Belleteste
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/loïc-belleteste-04b88b93
            </profile>
            <title>
                .NET programmer,
                worked with Gregory at Aptea
            </title>
            <text>
                "I have known Gregory Anne for three years I worked at Aptea. 
                He is a solid project manager who pays close attention to detail and actively follows through. 
                Thanks to his analysis and documentation, Gregory has successfully managed all his projects. 
                He is also a take-charge person who doesn't hesitate to help and advise others teams.
                Gregory has the abilities, desire and energy to make a significantand positive impact within any organization he becomes 
                involvedwith. I highly recommend him for employment in any organization."
                --June 15, 2015
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Bao Nguyen Minh
            </person>
            <profile>
                https://www.linkedin.com/in/beckerbao
            </profile>
            <title>
                Project Manager, IO Media
                worked with Gregory at IO-Network
            </title>
            <text>
                "Gregory gives me an impression when i worked with him. With "I can spirit", 
                he has created more usefull and fantastic applications for company. 
                I'm sure he is the right person for your successful IT's business."
                --May 18, 2011
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Hoai Anh Phan Nguyen
            </person>
            <profile>
                http://www.linkedin.com/pub/anh-phan/23/19b/245
            </profile>
            <title>
                Technical Project Manager, IO Media
                worked with Gregory at IO-Network
            </title>
            <text>
                "Gregory never feels satisfied with the current working process and technology of the company. He keeps seeking restlessly for improvements and his efforts usually remains in much more productive ways of working things out. 
                As a project manager, Gregory is best at project planning and risk management. After his first analysis and documentation, his staffs really have a clear direction to go. Projects under his management, therefore, are always delivered in time and in budget. 
                Being his colleage for more than 1 year, I also learn many good things from Gregory Anne, both in technical issues and management issues."
                --November 29, 2010
            </text>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Mahmoud Fatene
            </person>
            <profile>
                http://www.linkedin.com/pub/mahmoud-fatene/16/4b/5a4
            </profile>
            <title>
                Student, University Joseph Fourier (Grenoble I),
                studied with Gregory  at University Joseph-Fourier Grenoble I
            </title>
            <text>
                "I knew Gregory Anne as a student in university of Joseph Fourier, 
                during this period I came to notice his human qualities as well as his high 
                involvement in the projects in which we have worked together. He later on accomplished 
                very high achievements in his scolarity which for me was the logical rewards to all 
                his work. I, therefore, highly recommend Gregory Anne for both his personal and 
                professional aptitudes." --November 25, 2009
            </text>
        </item>
    </linkedin>
    <letters>
        <item>
            <person>
                Thomas Nguyen
            </person>
            <email>
                thomas@vn.ibm.com
            </email>
            <title>
                Project Manager, Web Development Competency Leader at IBM Vietnam
            </title>
            <letter>
                RecommendationLetter_GA_TN.pdf
            </letter>
        </item>
        <item>
            <person>
                Jean Caussanel
            </person>
            <email>
                jean.caussanel@univ-cezanne.fr
            </email>
            <title>
                Lecturer at Universite Aix-Marseille III
            </title>
            <letter>
                RecommendationLetter_GA_JC.pdf
            </letter>
        </item>
    </letters>
</referees>