<goals>
    <item>
        <title>
            Watch
        </title>
        <text>: I consider it as a must to keep myself up-to-date. <br/>
            Whatever could be the context I should be able to propose up-to-date technological solutions
            as well as up-to-date process guidelines.<br/>
            The informing as much as the getting informed has become an important quality and it enables my watch.<br/>
            <big>My permanent interest for technologies allows me today to be a leader in all the projects I am a part of,
                to unblock complicated situations, and to provide recommandations about development.</big>
            <br/>
            <br/>
        </text>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>
            Quality
        </title>
        <text>: My experience taught me that end-to-end development lifecycles should not be let up,
            internal projects might have their importance and need support because they keep people motivated,
            updated and efficient. 
            Continuous improvement attracts new opportunities when it comes to either business
            or the private concern of each contributor. <br/>
            <br/>
        </text>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>
            Participatory democracy
        </title>
        <text>: management has turned into coaching and encouraging,
            rather than ordering and directing. And that forces managers and leaders to be open
            to being taught by their employees. I believe this will be an appropriate teamwork orientation. 
            I also strongly believe <i>a chain is only as strong as its weakest link.</i> Team building is
            fundamental.<br/>
            <br/>
        </text>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>
            A bridge is to be created between East and West
        </title>
        <text>, I feel confident now I can be
            an actor in this play.</text>
    </item>
</goals>
